[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "rcerpudeo - Function without return value",
    "answer": "procedure"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "tcihsw - Executes code based on multiple values",
    "answer": "switch"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "ihelw - Loop that runs while condition true",
    "answer": "while"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "edhtar - Sequence of execution",
    "answer": "thread"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "ldpuoa - Sending program to device/server",
    "answer": "upload"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "lcmoeip - Converts source code to executable",
    "answer": "compile"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "collam - Allocates memory dynamically",
    "answer": "malloc"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "loccal - Allocates and zero-initializes memory",
    "answer": "calloc"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "ezosif - Gives size in bytes of a type or expression",
    "answer": "sizeof"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "uiclned - Brings in header files / declarations",
    "answer": "include"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "trnfip - Formatted output function",
    "answer": "printf"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "nsfac - Formatted input function",
    "answer": "scanf"
  }
]
